{
    "subject": "resource/Italian_Trans-Juba",
    "predicate": "property/currency",
    "object": "Italian lira",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Italian Trans-Juba is Italian lira.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9180575609207153,
            "question": "Is there any other currency besides the Italian lira used in Italian Trans-Juba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9135587811470032,
            "question": "What is the currency of Italian Trans-Juba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8623304963111877,
            "question": "What country uses the Italian lira as its currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8571197390556335,
            "question": "What are some common uses for the Italian lira in Italian Trans-Juba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8470864295959473,
            "question": "How stable is the value of the Italian lira in Italian Trans-Juba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8455546498298645,
            "question": "Are there any unique features of the Italian lira used in Italian Trans-Juba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8237180709838867,
            "question": "Is the Italian lira used in Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7345378994941711,
            "question": "What is the history behind the use of the Italian lira in Italian Trans-Juba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6688640713691711,
            "question": "What are the exchange rates for the Italian lira against other currencies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5813319683074951,
            "question": "Can you name a region that uses the Italian lira?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Italian Trans-Juba is Italian lira.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3980_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the exchange rates for the Italian lira against other currencies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3980_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history behind the use of the Italian lira in Italian Trans-Juba?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3980_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Italian lira used in Italy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3980_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3980_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The currency of Italian Trans-Juba is Italian lira.\" Specifically, the document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3980/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt` mentions:\n\n- \"currency = Italian Lira\" for Italian Trans-Juba.\n\nThis confirms that the currency used in Italian Trans-Juba was indeed the Italian lira."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}